startupjobs.asia 2015-12-28

# Privacy Statement of Startup Jobs Asia | StartUp Jobs Asia | Startup Hire | Startup Hiring | Startup Recruiting | Startup Jobs | VC Hire | VC Jobs | Work In Startups

  * Users of this website seeking employment shall be referred as " **Jobseekers** "
  * Users of the website seeking employees shall be referred as " **Employers** "
  * [www.startupjobs.asia](http://www.startupjobs.asia/) shall be referred as " **Website** "
  * Startup Jobs Asia Pte Ltd shall be referred as " **Company** "

The Company respects the privacy of the personal information/data of its users and will ensure compliance by its staff to the strictest standards of security and confidentiality in respect of all personal information/data submitted by users

Kindly read this privacy statement carefully to have an understanding of the Company’s policy and practices with regard to the treatment of personal information/data provided by users on the Website..

#### 1\. Purpose of Collection of Personal Information/Data

Users may be asked to provide personal information/data in the course of using the Website, although Users are not obliged to provide his/her personal information/data, the Company may not be able to render certain services on the Website in the event that Users fail to provide the required information/data.

The Company’s purposes for collecting the information/data on the Website are as follow:

  * assist Jobseekers to find appropriate employment with Employers
  * assist Employers to assess the suitability of candidates for a job vacancy
  * provide users with various services offered by the Website such as newsletter,electronic direct mail, information on job openings, promotional/marketing materials
  * contact users regarding administrative notices relevant to his/her account and usage of the Website
  * generate statistic about users to analyse usage of the Website in order to help further improvement of the Website

#### 2\. Collection of Personal Information/Data

Upon registration of a user account, the following information will be collected:

Jobseeker User Account

  * Name
  * Email(Used as Login ID)
  * Password for the User Account
  * Contact Number
  * Gender
  * Date of Birth
  * Current Location
  * Nationality
  * Education
  * Current Salary
  * Achievements / Summary
  * Resume & Working Experience History

Employer User Account

  * Startup Name
  * Country Startup Based in
  * Date Startup was found
  * Website of Startup
  * Name, Contact Number, Email (Used as Login ID) of Contact Person from Startup

Upon applying for any Job Advertisement on the Website and the Jobseeker is not a registered user on the Website, the following Jobseeker's personal information/data will be collected:

  * Email (Used as Login ID)
  * Name
  * Date of Birth
  * Gender
  * Contact Number
  * Education
  * Nationality
  * Achievements / Summary
  * Resume & Working Experience History

A Jobseeker user account will also be created for the Jobseeker if the Jobseeker is not a registered user on the Website, an email notification will be sent to the email address provided by the Jobseeker on the creation of the user account.

The Company shall not release such personal information/data to any third parties save and except in the circumstances listed under the section entitled "Disclosure or Transfer of Data" (below).

#### 3\. Disclosure or Transfer of Information/Data

The Company takes all practicable steps to keep all user personal information/data confidential and will only disclose or transfer such information and data in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

Upon applying to any Job Advertisements on the Website, the Jobseeker have given consent to the Company to disclose the Jobseeker’s personal information/data to the Employer posting the Job Advertisement and at the same time given consent to Employers registered with the Website to access his/her personal information/data in the database of the Website. Jobseeker can configure his/her personal information/data to only be accessible by Employers which the Jobseeker had applied for a job vacancy; this can be configured via the Edit Profile of the Jobseeker user account.

Any Jobseeker personal information/data obtained from the Website by the Employers shall only be used for the sole purpose of recruiting and assessing the suitability of Jobseekers, such personal information/data shall not be disclosed to any other parties without the prior consent of the Jobseeker concerned.

The Company may disclose/transfer personal information/data to third parties without user's prior consent under the following circumstances:

  * Jobseeker profile is set accessible by all Employers registered with the Website
  * maintenance of the database or facilitate the services on the Website by third party suppliers or service providers who have been authorized by the Company
  * in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations

By using the Website, users are deemed to have agreed/consented/authorized the disclosure/transfer of their personal information/data by the Company in the circumstances stated above.

#### 4\. Amendment & Changes to Personal Information/Data

Users can make amendments to her/her own personal information/data kept with the Company via their user account login. In the event that a user is unable to access or make amendments to his/her personal information/data via their user account login, he/she may contact the Company at this [link](http://www.startupjobs.asia/connect-with-us) for assistance, the Company may charge the user a reasonable fee for any request to change/modify/retrieve/remove/delete his/her personal information/data with the Company.

#### 5\. Cookie and Log Files

The Website does not collect any personally identifiable information from any user when they visit and browse the Website; the Website only records their visit with details as follow:

  * Domain Name Server (DNS) & Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * Tracking of pages user visits
  * Browser type used to access the Website
  * Referring/Exiting Pages
  * Operation System
  * Date/Time Stamp

All of these are done without users being aware that they are occurring, data collected in the above manner are not link to any personally identifiable information. The Company uses such automatically collected information and data to estimate the audience size of the Website, track number of entries in the Company’s promotional activities and measure users' traffic patterns.

#### 6\. Update & Changes in this Privacy Statement

The Company reserves the right to update, revise, modify or amend this Statement at any time as the Company deems necessary without prior notice, and users are strongly advised to review this Statement frequently. If the Company decides to update, revise, modify or amend this Statement, the Company will post those changes to this webpage and/or other places as the Company deems appropriate, so that users will be aware of what information the Company collects, how the Company uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, the Company discloses it.
